A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Special Collections Publications FA1395
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Library Reference Materials, 1948-2009; 2
  - Ukrainian Communism and Soviet Russian Policy Toward the Ukraine: An Annotated Bibliography, Jurij Lawrynenko, Research Program on the USSR (East European Fund), 1953 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - First, Second, and Third Annual Reports of the East European Fund, 1951-1954 (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - Guide to the National Merit Scholarship Program, 1961 August (Box 23, Folder 240)
  - Independent Financing of Scholarship Aid, The National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1955 September 8 (Box 23, Folder 241)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation Annual Reports, 1956-1964 (Box 23, Folder 242-250)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation Annual Report: The Merit Program: The First Decade, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation Annual Report, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation 20th Annual Report, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corporation Annual Report, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories, Inc. First Annual Report: Here They Learn, 1959 November (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - The Things of Education: A Second Report from Educational Facilities Laboratories, Inc., 1961 (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Grants and Projects 1961-1963: Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1964 June (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Campus in the City: A Report from Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 258)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories 1969 Annual Report: Transformation of the Schoolhouse (Box 24, Folder 259)
  - The Purposes and Activities of Educational Facilities Laboratories pamphlet, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 260)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories 1970 Annual Report (Box 24, Folder 261)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories 1972 Annual Report (Box 24, Folder 262)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories 1973 Report (Box 24, Folder 263)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories 1974 Annual Report (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Publications, Films, and Services pamphlet, Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1977 September (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories (EFL): A Foundation in Transition, The Purposes, Programs, and Publications of Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - The Teaching of Economics in Mexico, Occasional Report No. 1, Education and World Affairs, Blanca M. de Petricioli and Clark Winton Reynolds, 1967 January (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - Guidelines for the Planning of External Aid Projects in Education, Occasional Report No. 2, Education and World Affairs, Arthur J. Lewis, 1967 January (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - Educational Development in Africa: The Role of United States Assistance, Occasional Report No. 4, Education and World Affairs, John W. Masland, 1967 June (Box 24, Folder 269)
  - US University Activity Abroad: Implications of the Mexican Case, Occasional Report No. 5, Education and World Affairs, Charles Myers, 1968 April (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Problems of Professional Identity: An Examination of Training for Human Resource Development and Educational Planning, Occasional Paper No. 6, Education and World Affairs, Adam Curle, 1968 July (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Internationalizing the US Professional School, Occasional Report No. 9, Education and World Affairs, 1969 September (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - Education and World Affairs: Report on Program, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Education and World Affairs, 1963 April (Box 25, Folder 274)
  - A Crisis of Dollars: The Funding Threat to International Affairs in US Higher Education, A Report from Education and World Affairs, 1968 September (Box 25, Folder 275)
  - The Professional School and World Affairs: Report of the Task Force on Law, A Report from Education and World Affairs, 1967 June (Box 25, Folder 276)
  - The Professional School and World Affairs, A Report from Education and World Affairs, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 277)
  - The University and World Affairs, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 278)
  - The College and World Affairs, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 279)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. 1st Annual Report - 8th Annual Report, 1957 June 30-1964 June 30 (Box 25, Folder 280-287)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. 9th Annual Report - 14th Annual Report, 1965 June 30 - 1970 June 30 (Box 26, Folder 288-293)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc. 16th Annual Report, 1972 June 30 (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Reports of Projects and Publications Resulting from Projects, Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1960 January (Box 26, Folder 295)
  - Press Release - Establishment of the Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1956 September 19 (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Energy in the American Economy 1850-1975: An Economic Study of Its History and Prospects, Resources for the Future, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 297)
    Signed to David E. Bell from Joseph Lerner (author of Part II)
  - The Natural Resource Content of US Foreign Trade 1970-1955, Jaroslav Vanek, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - The Changing World Market for Iron Ore, 1950-1980: An Economic Geography, Gerald Manners, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Resources and People in East Kentucky: Problems and Potentials of a Lagging Economy, Mary Jean Bowman and W. Warren Haynes, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Statistical Annex: Compilation of Statistical Data on UN Leadership Posts; Discussion Paper #1: Improving the Process: Finding the Most Effective Leaders; Discussion Paper #2: Organizing UN Leadership in the 1990s, undated (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Academe: Bulletin of the American Association of University Professors, 2006 July-August (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - Rural Community College Initiative (RCCI) pamphlet, undated (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - Reproductive Health, AIDS and Gender Violence as Global Issues: Beyond Borders, Reproductive Health Affinity Group Meeting, Salvador, Bahia, Brazil, 1999 October 9-14 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - US Energy Policies: An Agenda for Research, A Resources for the Future Staff Report, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - Changing Lives, Changing Communities: Oral Histories from Action for Boston Community Development, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - The Granada Guildhall Lectures 1982: The Liberty of the Citizen, Franklin Thomas, John Mortimer, and Lord Hunt of Tanworth, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - Communications Policy and Information Technology: Promises, Problems, Prospects, Edited by Lorrie Faith Cranor and Shane Greenstein, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 308)
    Note from Benjamin M. Compaine enclosed
    Grant #1015-0486
  - The Great Society: Lessons for the Future, Edited by Eli Ginzberg and Robert M. Solow, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - Las Naciones Unidas En Su Segundo Cincuentenario: Informe del Grupo de Trabajo Independiente sobre el futuro de las Naciones Unidas, undated (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - The Future of the International Economic Order: An Agenda for Research, C. Fred Bergsten, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Investment in Innovation: An Historical Appraisal of the Fund for the Advancement of Education, Paul Woodring, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 312)
  - A World in Need of Leadership: Tomorrow's United Nations, A Fresh Appraisal, Brian Urquhart and Erskine Childers, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 313)
  - New Energy Technologies for Buildings: Institutional Problems and Solutions, Richard Schoen, Alan Hirshberg, and Jerome Weingart, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 314)
  - Backs Against the Wall: Urban-Oriented Colleges and Universities and the Urban Poor and Disadvantaged, Pastora San Juan Cafferty and Gail Spangenberg, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 315)
    Ford Foundation Series on Higher Education in the Cities
  - Signs of Promise: Stories of Philanthropic Leadership in Advancing Regional and Neighborhood Equity, Funders' Network for Smart Growth and Livable Communities, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 316)
  - Transforming Students' Lives: How "Exploring Transfer" Works, and Why by Janet Lieberman and Julie Yearsley Hungar, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 317)
    The story of the "Exploring Transfer" program initiated from a collaboration between Vassar College and LaGuardia Community College
  - The Power of Partnerships: A Guide for Practitioners and Policymakers, Experiences and Lessons Drawn from Collaboration Between Governmental and Nongovernmental Organizations, The Partnership Project of the National Association of Development Organizations Research Foundation, 1998 April (Box 29, Folder 318)
  - Who Speaks for the Hungry? How FAO Elects Its Leaders, Charles H. Weitz, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 319)
  - The United Nations in Its Second Half-Century: The Report of the Independent Working Group of the Future of the United Nations, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 320)
  - They Went to College Early: Evaluation Report Number 2, Established by the Ford Foundation, The Fund for Adult Education, 1957 April (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - The Male Role in Teenage Pregnancy and Parenting: New Directions for Public Policy, Vera Institute of Justice, Inc., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - The Miami Riot of 1980: Crossing the Bounds, Bruce Porter and Marvin Dunn, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 323)
    Contains book's press release
  - The Legal Foundations of American Philanthropy, 1776-1884, Howard S. Miller, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - Television and the Child: An Empirical Study of the Effect of Television on the Young, Hilde Himmelweit, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - Management Education in Spain, William C. Frederick and Chadwick J. Haberstroh, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - Mapping Our Places: Voices from the Indigenous Communities Mapping Initiative, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 846)
  - Origins, Journeys and Returns: Social Justice in International Higher Education, Edited by Toby Alice Volkman with John Dassin and Mary Zurbuchen, Social Science Research Council, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - Social Science Research on Business: Product and Potential, Robert A. Dahl, Mason Haire, and Paul F. Lazarsfeld, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 328)
  - Social Science Research Council, Kenton W. Worcester, 1923-1998, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 329)
  - Social Science and Power in Indonesia, Edited by Vedi R. Hadiz and Daniel Dhakidae, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 330)
  - Healing the Heart of the Cities: Young Voices Speak Out, A Project of the Campus Outreach Opportunity League, Edited by Sean Dennis Cashman, 1992 August (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - African Studies in the United States: A Perspective, Jane I. Guyer, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - La Second Demi-Siecle de L'Organisation des Nations Unies, Rapport du Groupe de Travail Independant sur l'avenir de l'Organisation des Nations Unies, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 333)
  - Research Universities and the National Interest: A Report from Fifteen University Presidents, 1977 December (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - Integrating Intellectual Property Rights and Development Policy, Report of the Commission on Intellectual Property Rights, 2002 September (Box 32, Folder 335)
  - Charters of Philanthropies: A Study of Selected Trust Instruments, Charters, By-Laws, and Court Decisions, M. M. Chambers, The Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 336)
  - Global Media Governance: A Beginner's Guide, Sean O. Siochru and Bruce Girard with Amy Mahan, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 337)
  - Strategic Media: Designing A Public Interest Campaign, Strategic Communications for Nonprofits, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 338)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Talk Radio, Pat Aufderheide and Jeffrey Chester, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 339)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Voice Programs, Christine Brim, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 340)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Op-Eds: A Cost-Effective Strategy for Advocacy, Denice Zeck and Edmund Rennolds, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 341)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Using Video: The VCR Revolution for Nonprofits, Eloise Payne, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 342)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Media Advocacy: Reframing Public Debate, Michael Pertschuk and Phillip Wilbur, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 343)
  - Benton Foundation: Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Cable Access: Community Channels and Productions for Nonprofits, Margie Nicholson, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 344)
  - Strategic Communications for Nonprofits: Introducing a Series of Media Guides, Published by Benton Foundation and Center for Strategic Communications, Edited by Larry Kirkman and Karen Menichelli, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 345)
  - Electronic Networking for Nonprofit Groups: A Guide to Getting Started by Tom Sherman, Strategic Communications for Nonprofits, A Publication of Apple Computer Community Affairs and Benton Foundation, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 346)
  - The Last Years of Apartheid: Civil Liberties in South Africa, John Dugard, Nicholas Haysom, and Gilbert Marcus, South Africa Update Series, Ford Foundation - Foreign Policy Association, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 347)
  - Un Mundo en Necesidad de Conduccion, Las Naciones Unidas Del Manana, Brian Urquhart and Erskine Childers, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 348)
  - Technical Assistance and Innovation in Science Education, Robert H. Maybury, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 349)
  - Women...A World Survey, Ruth Leger Sivard, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 350)
  - Women: Roles and Status in Eight Countries (Egypt, Bangladesh, Mexico, Ghana, Japan. France, United States, Poland), Edited by Janet Zollinger Giele and Audrey Chapman Smock, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 351)
  - US Foreign Policy and the United Nations System, Edited by Charles William Maynes and Richard S. Williamson, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 352)
  - Nurturing Young Black Males: Challenges to Agencies, Programs, and Social Policy, Ronald B. Mincy, Editor, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 353)
  - Research and Evaluation: Needs for the Future, Lyle Saunders, Proceedings of The International Conference on Family Planning Programs, Geneva; Reprinted from Family Planning and Population Programs: A Review of World Development, 1965 August (Box 33, Folder 354)
  - Sowing the Green Revolution, International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, Ibadan, Nigeria, 1970 April (Box 33, Folder 355)
  - French Development Assistance: A Study in Policy and Administration, Richard C. Robarts, Sage Professional Papers in Administrative and Policy Studies, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 356)
  - Honoring Contributions in the Governance of American Indian Nations: Celebrating Excellence in Tribal Governance, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 357)
  - Justice and Conservation: Insights from People, Plants and Justice: The Politics of Nature Conservation, Charles Zerner, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 358)
  - America's Wealthy and the Future of Foundations, Teresa Odendahl, Editor, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 359)
  - The Underclass, Ken Auletta, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 360)
  - South Africa: Time is Running Out, The Report of the Study Commission on US Policy Toward Southern Africa, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 361)
  - People, Population, and Policy in Indonesia, Edited by Terence H. Hull (2 copies; 1 English, 1 Indonesian), 2005, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 362-363)
  - Pour Renover le Systeme des Nations Unies, Erskine Childers avec Brian Urquhart, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 364)
- Fund for Adult Education (FAE) Publications, 1934-2010; 3
  - Alumni Education for Public Responsibility, Arden House Conference, 1961 February 23-25 (Box 35, Folder 365)
  - How to Organize and Manage Series of Adult Discussion Programs, The Fund for Adult Education, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 366)
  - How to Organize and Manage a Series of Adult Study Discussion Programs, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 367)
  - The Future of Study-Discussion Programs, A Joint Statement by: The Great Books Foundation, American Foundation for Political Education, The Fund for Adult Education, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 368)
  - Tomorrow's Professors: A Report of the College Faculty Internship Program, John S. Diekhoff, The Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 369)
  - College in the Country: A Program of Education for Adults, Mildred E. English, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 370)
  - Toward the Liberally Educated Executive, Robert A. Goldwin and Charles A. Nelson, The Fund for Adult Education, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 371)
  - Education: The Challenge Ahead, Edited by C. Scott Fletcher, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 372)
    Autographed to Henry Heald from Scotty Fletcher
  - Education for Public Responsibility, Edited by C. Scott Fletcher, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 373)
  - Education for Public Responsibility: A Statement by the Directors of the Fund for Adult Education, undated (Box 36, Folder 374)
  - Education for Public Responsibility: Information for Officers of National Organization, undated (Box 36, Folder 375)
  - Accent on Learning: An Analytical History of the Fund for Adult Education's Experimental Discussion Project, 1951-1959, Glen Burch, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 376)
  - Able People Well Prepared: The Adult Education and the Mass Media Fellowship Programs - 1952-1961 of the Fund for Adult Education, Ronald Shilen (Box 36, Folder 377)
  - The Perkins Lectures, Fund for Adult Education, 1956 April (Box 36, Folder 378)
  - The Randall Lectures, The Fund for Adult Education Annual Lectureship, 1957 January (Box 36, Folder 379)
  - The Redfield Lectures, Robert Redfield, Fund for Adult Education, 1955 April (Box 36, Folder 380)
  - The Bryson Lectures: The Task of Liberal Adult Education, Lyman Bryson, The Fund for Adult Education, 1954 May (Box 36, Folder 381)
  - Aging in the Modern World: Selections from the Literature of Aging for Pleasure and Instruction, A Book of Readings Compiled by Clark Tibbitts, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 382)
  - Aging in the Modern World: Study Discussion Series for Adults, A Handbook for Group Members, Prepared Under the Direction of Clark Tibbitts and Wilma Donahue, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 383)
  - Topics and Texts: Human Freedom Compiled by Shirley R. Letwin for the Fund for Adult Education Established by the Ford Foundation, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 384)
  - Great Books and Small Groups, James A. Davis, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    Signed by James A. Davis
  - The Effect on Minnesota of a Liberalization of United States Foreign Trade Policy, Report of Business Executives' Research Committee Study Sponsored by the University of Minnesota, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 386)
  - Public School Adult Education: A Guide for Administrators and Teachers, A Publication of the National Association of Public School Adult Educators, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 387)
  - The Challenge of Lifetime Learning, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 388)
  - Adult Experience and College Degrees: A Report of the Experimental Degree Project for Adults at Brooklyn College, 1954-1958, Bernard H. Stern and Ellswerth Missall, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 389)
  - Work Study College Programs: Appraisal and Report of the Study of Cooperative Education, James W. Wilson and Edward H. Lyons, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 390)
  - St. Paul Public Schools Survey of Organization and Management, Cresap, McCormick and Paget Management Consultants, 1959 July (Box 37, Folder 391)
  - St. Paul Public Schools Projection of Secondary School Plant and Financial Requirements, Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Management Consultants, 1959 July (Box 38, Folder 392)
  - The Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation: Origin and Early Operations, Edward M. Brecher, 1978 February (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - From the Ground Up: Building Assets Through Development Finance pamphlet, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 394)
  - The Power to Govern: A Series of Experimental Study and Discussion Programs on the Separation of Powers in the American System of Government, Peter H. Odegard and Victor G. Rosenblum, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 395)
  - New Directions for Adult Education, Proceedings: Conference of Administrative Officers and Deans of Syracuse University, Introduction by Alexander N. Charters, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 396)
  - The New Mass Media: Challenge to a Free Society, Gilbert Seldes, American Association of University Women, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 397)
    Signed to Frances Butler from Gilbert Seldes
  - Management Education for Itself and Its Employees: Part I - Management Education in American Business: General Summary, Lyndall F. Urwick, American Management Association, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 398)
  - Management Education for Itself and Its Employees: Part II - A Survey of Management Development: The Quantitative Aspects, Joseph M. Trickett, American Management Association, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 399)
  - Management Education for Itself and Its Employees: Part III - Case Studies in Management Development: Theory and Practice in Ten Selected Companies, Robert G. Simpson, American Management Association, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 400)
  - Management Education for Itself and Its Employees: Part IV - The Education of Employees: A Status Report: With a Proposal for Further Research, Douglas Williams and Stanley Peterfreund, American Management Association, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 401)
  - The Power to Govern: Notes for Discussion Leaders, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 402)
  - Occasional Papers Number 1 - Residential Colleges: Some New Developments in British Adult Education, Guy Hunter, The Fund for Adult Education, undated (Box 39, Folder 403)
  - Occasional Papers Number 2 - Adult Education in Australia, Fred Alexander, The Fund for Adult Education, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 404)
  - Occasional Papers Number 3 - Adult Education in Citizenship In Postwar Germany, Alice Hanson Cook, The Fund for Adult Education, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 405)
  - Politics 1960, Edited by Francis M. Carney and H. Frank Way, Jr. (Box 39, Folder 406)
  - An Overview of Adult Education Research, Edmund deS, Brunner and Associates, Adult Education Association, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 407)
  - Public Leadership: A Critical Review with Special Reference to Adult Education, Wendell Bell, Richard J. Hill, and Charles R. Wright, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 408)
  - Liberal Adult Education, The Fund for Adult Education, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 409)
    Five speeches from the Community Leadership Institute at the Stanley Hotel in Estes Park, Colorado in July 1956
  - Participation in Adult Education: Based on the October 1957 Current Population Survey, Circular No. 539, Bureau of the Census, Office of Education, Marie D. Wann and Marthine V. Woodward, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 410)
  - Organizing Study-Discussion Groups in the Liberal Arts, The Fund for Adult Education, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 411)
  - In Quest of Knowledge: A Historical Perspective on Adult Education, C. Hartley Grattan, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 412)
  - Learning Comes of Age, John Walker Powell, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 413)
  - Studies in Adult Group Learning in the Liberal Arts, Programs, Participants, and Effects Four Book Set, 1957-1960 (Box 40, Folder 414)
    Research in Adult Group Learning in the Liberal Arts by John Walker Powell; Study Discussion in the Liberal Arts by Abbott Kaplan; A Comparative Study of Lecture and Discussion Methods by Richard J. Hill; A Study of Participants in the Great Books Program, James A. Davis
  - University Extension in the United States: A Study by the National University Extension Association, Made with the Assistance of a Grant from the Fund for Adult Education, John R. Morton, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Universities and Unions in Workers' Education, Jack Barbash, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 415)
  - Rural Social Systems and Adult Education, Resulting from a Study Sponsored by the The Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities and The Fund for Adult Education Established by the Ford Foundation, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 416)
  - Businessmen in Government: An Appraisal of Experience, 1958 May (Box 41, Folder 417)
  - Basic Issues of Man Volume 1 - The Nature of Man, Rollin Chambliss, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 418)